Good afternoon. You're watching DPRO
with Ted R and John Kuryaku. I'm
editorial cartoonist Ted R. CIA
whistleblower John Kuryaku is my co-host
and my co-pilot in this like in this
game we call life
the next hour of the news.
>> Not that there's anything wrong with
that.
>> No, not at all. Nothing at all. Um, so
uh the FBI is still looking for Charlie
Kirk's murderer. We'll be getting into
that and exactly uh you know what comes
next. Um the former president of Brazil,
Jaier Bolsinaro, has pro whose first
name I'm probably mispronouncing, has uh
just been convicted on all five counts,
including plotting uh to overturn the
2022 election. We'll get into that. Um I
really want to talk to you, John, about
this story about the Venezuelan boat uh
air. Uh it's just got me fuming. Yeah.
And uh some news that I didn't think I
would ever say ever again. Iran Contra
is back in the news.
>> I know. That's the best news of the day.
>> It is the best news of the day.
>> It is. I'm liking it.
>> So, uh it is Thursday, September 11th,
2025. Thanks for joining us here on
Drogram. Please like, follow, and share
the show. Please chime in with uh your
comments and questions. We will get to
all of the ones that we can. Um, I gotta
say there's a very the very first one,
John, before we get into it. I want to
answer this or I think we should both
answer it. Um, from another wonderful
secret. The Republican party controls
all three branches of government. Can
they do anything to help us? This was
supposed to be their big chance. What
happened? Why does everything keep
getting worse?
>> Good question. Yeah, I you know, the
Republicans will tell you, well,
uh, we, um, we would need 60 votes in
the Senate to break closure, so we're
kind of jammed up there, and our
majority is so small in the House, and
the Republicans just lost two uh,
interim elections last week for the
House, so it's tighter than ever, blah
blah blah blah blah. The truth is that
um there's no coordinated policy. And
even though Donald Trump is a strong
political leader within his own party,
he's not quite strong enough to force
the the uh the uh Freedom Caucus people
to do what he wants.
>> Uh yeah, I also think that u there's a
lot more of the old Republican party
baked into
>> coming back to the new Republican party
than anyone, including the president,
would like to admit. Um, and so, you
know, there's it's the country club
Republicans still running the show. They
still want to cut taxes to the wealthy.
They still want to get rid of social
programs. They still want to suck up to
big business and defense contractors.
They still want to pour money into the
military-industrial complex.
>> They're not really a different party
than they were in 1986. There's just
>> You're right.
>> You're right. And and that's coming out.
It's like the the neocons ran for cover
in 2016 and they just started coming out
of their hiding places and they haven't
been squashed back down.
>> Sadly, they're becoming more and more
bold. But I think you're right, Ted. I
think what's happening here, and it's
it's relatively slow motion. It's taken
a little bit of time, but I think what's
going to happen is the old Republican
party is going to come back once Donald
Trump is gone and they're going to be
the ones in charge again. MAGA is a
temporary situation.
>> Yeah. MAGA is a style.
>> Good way to put it. Yeah.
>> It's it's not an ideological
orientation. I mean, and I can just ask
this, you know, for example, if I ask
any real MAGA adherent, well, it's about
making America great again. Okay. What
does that mean specifically? I mean, and
I'm not trying to be snotty. Those are
deliberately It's a brilliant phrase
because it's deliberately vague. It can
mean anything you say. I mean, you know,
if it's like things that basically it's
things that Donald Trump wants to do.
>> Yes.
>> And that's going to get old
>> after a while. I agree. Um, we got a
question here, personal question about
the show from Jay Herna. Any chance
Michelle returns once you start pulling
in the big bucks?
Yeah, I doubt it. You know, I Michelle
and I text each other, but it's always
just interesting articles that we find
or she texted me a joke the other day
she thought I I would find funny, but I
don't I don't think she really wants to
come back. She hasn't said anything to
me. Has she said anything to you?
>> No, she hasn't. Um I haven't really I
mean, we're still we're we're Facebook
friends. I see. Yeah, she's been doing a
lot of traveling.
>> Yeah, she's been doing a lot of
traveling. So, I think she's uh you
know, I mean, if that comes up, we'll
talk about it, you know, but there's
it's not like there's any dark secrets
and we're certainly we haven't been
keeping her under wraps. She's not in
Area 51 or anything like that.
>> No, that's right.
>> Uh do we think that the We have a Thank
you for the donation from Fuso. Uh, do
we think that the uh Charlie Kirk
assassination could be a deep state
false flag operation that will unite the
right and get them off their demands for
the Epstein files?
>> I I doubt it. No,
>> I think this is like I think this is a
dist a person obviously I'm going to say
disturbed because you have to be
>> you have to be right. Seriously.
>> So, you know, I mean even if you're not
like swallowing your own tongue or
whatever, you're still to do this to go
and do this kind of Ted, I I'm I'm
giving a talk tonight at this 911 truth
event that I didn't realize was 911
truth when I agreed to do it. Um, but
anyway, I was I there was a lunch that
went along with it today and I was
sitting next to this guy and he wanted
to talk about Charlie Kirk. So, we're
talking about Charlie Kirk. It is
terrible. It's awful. I can't believe it
happened. There's no excuse. They're
blaming the victim. Blah blah blah. And
he says, "Yeah, but he thinks he has
this figured out." He says the shot was
perfectly at the juggler from a distance
of 200 meters. Who's good at those kind
of pinpointed
uh attacks? The Israelis. This is a
Mossad operation. I And I just said,
"Stop. Please
>> just just stop. Please. I'm not going to
have this conversation. Just stop." You
know, unfortunately, look, I love
spaghetti westerns, but like movies like
Hang Them High and like uh The Good,
Bad, and The Ugly where they have where
the guy shoots the rope from like, I
don't know, 400 yards away. Um I mean,
you're supposed to under I think that
when those movies were made, most
viewers were familiar enough with guns
to know that it was kind of a joke and
kind of impossible. And now I think
people think that stuff's real. They
think that Bob Odenkirk can have the
[__] beaten out of him. Yeah. And he's
not alive. He's not dead or anything.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're exactly right.
Yes.
>> It's I mean the the thing is the guy got
the shot off obviously, right? I assume
she fired at the head. I mean, but
basically if the shot you shoot at
someone's head and you hit any part of
their body,
>> you're gonna kill.
>> That's a good job. You did, you know,
you did what you you came for. You don't
get aim for a specific part of the body
like that. Aim for the for the I mean
that's just a I can't say lucky I mean
you know but it's a
>> it's a very precise I don't even know
it's not precise it's just that that's
where it struck.
>> Yes that's all.
>> John Doe NXCI officer attending a
conference called 911 truth. I know man
this is killing me.
>> I know it's an honorarium
>> which is the only reason I was doing it.
It's $500 I didn't have yesterday. And
then my manager is like, "What?"
$10,000. Okay. He said, "I'm gonna
strangle you for taking $500."
>> I kind of think your man I'm on your I'm
on team manager here. Um yeah, I don't
think it's enough money there.
Everyone's got a price and I'm I'm one
of those people, but you know that price
is not high enough.
>> You know, I'll tell you a secret.
>> You're gonna be upset by But in three
hours from now, you're going to be not
happy.
>> You're exactly right. Besides the fact
that it's at 9:45 p.m. and I'm usually
winded down by then.
>> Oh, [__] I'm asleep by then.
>> I know, right? But uh I I just I saw
something on eBay that I wanted and I
thought, "Ah, here's an easy 500. I'll
just do that."
>> I kick myself.
>> Well, let's see. Adam Fighter says, "I
think you guys need to address this.
People are conflating speaking
negatively about Charlie Kirk's opinions
and celebrating his death.
>> It's a good point.
>> I agree with that. Look, I'm I'm
probably No one has probably is probably
more famous in this country for speaking
ill of the dead than me. I mean,
>> you've been in trouble for it.
>> I did. I said I said bad things about
people like President Reagan the day
that he died. I said I said he's turning
Krispy Brown by now. Sean Hannity
couldn't stop talking about it. said,
"You have no soul." What he said was
like coming from Sean Hannity. He he
wouldn't know his soul if it bit him in
his ass. But um you know Pat Tilman,
lots of people. And um and the point is
uh and I was kind of famous for my anti-
uh for my anti- um obituaries that kind
of call into question people who were
well highly regarded and you know
revisited them like Jimmy Carter and
people like that. Okay. So there is no
better time to assess someone's life
than at the time of their death. And for
a public figure like Charlie Kirk, Ted
Ra, or John Kiryaku, the time of our
death is the time when what we've said
and done will be assessed and should be
assessed. It's appropriate. Um, and it's
very different to say, um, you know,
like, look, I'm not glad that he's dead,
right?
>> And I'm not even glad that he's not that
his voice has been silenced. Um, you
know, and I don't agree or like a lot of
the things that he said. And I think you
should be able to just say like, you can
even say like this guy was an [__]
>> Yeah.
>> Um, and and but no one should have
killed that [__] You can say that. I
think that's totally fine.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I agree with that. You
know, I I've gotten in trouble, too, for
for obituaries that I've written for
Covert Action Magazine. Anytime somebody
associated with the CIA's torture
program dies, I write a really
mean-spirited alternative obituary
saying that the world is better off
without them in it. And um and I wrote
one three or four years ago where the
guy's daughter called me.
>> Oh [__]
>> And she was like, "Shame on you, you
monster." And I said I said, "You want
to see a monster? Take a look at at your
at your father and imagine the people
that he murdered. sorry, but uh you
know, now's not the time to try to
pretty things up. He had that
opportunity in 2002 and he elected to be
with the bad guys.
>> By the way, Candace Strike, I have no
opinion about whether uh Charlie Kirk
was a nice guy or not because I
literally the only thing I only knew
about him in the abstract. Um I kn I
lost track of him after he founded
Turning Point and um you know, I didn't
even know he'd become this big
influencer and he was huge and all that.
So, oh,
>> I have no I had to look him up and be
like and I was like, "Oh, yeah. He's
that guy,
>> you know? I mean, I don't really follow
all the people on the in the right-wing,
you know, uh,
>> for whatever reason, he's in my TikTok
feed like every fourth or fifth short
for the last two years." Um, and because
I'm, you know, on my knees begging for a
pardon from these these MAGA people, um,
I've been sort of in the on the on the
edge of the same circle. And everybody
says the same thing that he was a real
sweetheart as a as a person. He was just
a really great guy.
>> You know, I've not met him.
>> You never know. Okay. So, like Bill
O'Reilly,
>> he was a really nice man to me. So nice.
really I found him to be such a dick
>> now. Like and well, what happened was he
had been a dick and then I was getting
all these death threats and I I was on
his show all the time. I I had a I had a
frequent flyer pass at Fox News
Security. Um and they uh and one time
before the show, he's like, "Ted, I hear
a lot of things on my end, really bad
things, and I'm worried about you. I
think I'm worried that someone's gonna
do something to you. if you ever want to
get out of the city and you just need a
place to I have a house upstate. It's
yours for as long as you want. Just take
it and go. I was like, Bill, thank you
so much.
>> Wow.
>> It was really
>> I'm astounded by that.
>> I I think I figured you would be.
>> Yeah.
>> He was such an ass to me. I I can't even
imagine the words coming out of his
mouth.
>> I know. I I mean, this was after I'd
been on like 20 times and he'd always
been a dick to me. Um, but I think
there's there was a certain point that
he just I think that the the the
killing, the the death threats, it just
went too far for him.
>> You know, I was on that BBC show Cross
Talk, I think it's called. It's like the
60 Minutes of of the UK.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, I think it's called Cross Talk.
>> Well, there was there was the RT show
Cross Talk.
>> Not not the RT show,
>> which was a great show, by the way.
>> It was the BBC. It was Yeah. But the BBC
show. I forget what it's called now, but
um anyway, I was warned in advance
they're going to just take you apart.
It's what they do. And um and they did.
Man, I went on and I felt just like
crying at the end of it. Although I I
held I held my own. And then when we
finished it before we we went off, the
guy says, "Hey, uh, I heard you got an
award in London and in the event that
you can't come because I know you have
some travel restrictions. I'm happy to
accept the award on your behalf." And I
was like, "Oh, okay. You just called me
some of the most horrible things that
anybody's ever called me in my life,
but okay." And then I actually was
denied entry into the UK. So I got
>> Jace, by the way, says that this show is
called Hard Talk.
>> Hard Talk.
>> And I remember this show. I've seen this
show.
>> Thank you.
>> It's great, by the way.
>> It's And it it is great.
>> But you got to go in there ready.
>> Those are [__] Brits, man. When the
Brits mix it up, they're not They don't
come with any hands tied behind their
backs.
>> That's right.
>> They're funny and smart as [__]
>> He went to the uh He went to the event.
Actually, it's the one behind me right
there. That that glass thing with the
blue glass inside the clear glass.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Um, he went and accepted the award for
me and then he mailed it. It cost like
$150 to mail it at his own expense.
>> I am with Adam Fighter that this we we
are describing borderline personality
behavior. I mean, that's exactly what it
is. Um,
>> that's so true. Uh, by the way, um,
okay, so donation from from F F Huso
seemed like a professional hit. One shot
and gone. I disagree with that. I think
it was a lucky hit and there was no
point doing a second shot.
>> What do you think?
>> You know, I think that you're right,
Ted, and I think that we're making too
much of the fact that it hit his
juggler.
>> I think they he was probably aiming for
the head or the neck or the chest or
whatever. He was off just a little bit.
>> And um
>> Oh, yeah. Was it was it a long enough
range that he he he targeted a little
high?
>> I think so.
>> Might have been a little wind. Who
knows? Um, okay. So, Jones Jameson, not
to be confused with James Jones. Uh,
thanks for the donation. What do we
think of the House Rules Committee
blocking a vote to end selective
service? Will the potential for another
draft ever go away? And by the way, I'll
let me add a question to that for you,
John. How the [__] can America's women
live with themselves and call themselves
feminists and not insist that they be
drafted alongside men?
>> That's an oped right there. And you are
100% right. Either we're we're all
feminists who support equality or we're
not.
>> And I can't believe I can't believe this
this thing. Yeah. My son could be
drafted into one of America's myriad of
idiotic wars, but his girlfriend can't
be. Really? Ridiculous.
>> No. No. I agree. You know, I said
something on Facebook about a year ago
that, you know, I I consider myself a
feminist, but the way I was raised, you
hold the door open for a woman. And I
would
>> I hold the door open for men, too,
though.
>> I I do, too. I hold the door open for
men, too. But I I feel uncomfortable
about a woman paying for a date to the
point where I just won't allow it to
happen.
>> Well, especially like especially a first
date. Yeah,
>> especially. But for me, it's any date. I
It's I just can't do it. And then a
friend of mine from college, a woman
answered like, "How dare you? I am your
equal in every way. And if we ever went
on a date, I would demand to pay at
least half." And I said, "Well, What's
her number? No, I'm just kidding.
>> She's happily married with a with a 20
25 year old son. And I said, maybe
that's why we never met. We never went
out because I I just wouldn't,
>> you know. But other than that, I think
you're exactly right, Ted. Either we're
going to have the draft for everybody or
we have the draft for nobody.
>> And I don't see how it's constitutional
under the 14th amendment equal
protection clause. I I just don't I
agree.
>> Um we got Okay, we got a lot of comments
here. Um and I guess we're
>> Oh, questions. Okay. It's from Soden 20.
What's your What's your uh Oh,
>> we have a lot of questions.
>> Oh, yeah. Okay. Soden 24. John and Ted,
>> what do you think about the Qatari prime
minister saying that BB is deliberately
trying to plunge the Middle East into
chaos?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, I think he's 100% right.
>> 100%.
>> And do you think more Arab nations will
speak out against him and his
government?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I do.
>> It's coming. It's coming. Once one of
the big ones does, once the Egyptians or
the Saudis say something, it's going to
open the floodgates. And I think there's
actually I think there's actually
pressure on a lot of the big Arab
governments from the likes of France and
Ireland and Canada and maybe Australia.
So I I think that's coming.
>> Egypt would be a big deal.
>> That would be a big one.
>> Uh and then Jacob Decker, thanks for the
donation. Killing someone speaking a
different point of view is an attack on
the first amendment. You're here
>> 100%
>> couldn't agree more. And I would now
okay now. Okay. Here I'm going to be a
cynical bastard here.
>> If this had happened to me, I sincerely
doubt that Charlie Kirk would have gone
on to a pod his podcast and deplored
what happened to me. I sincerely doubt
it. And I sincerely doubt that the
president would uh have the flags at
half at a half mass for me and through
until Sunday. And I seriously doubt that
my dead ass would be getting a
presidential medal of freedom.
>> Yeah. I
>> I mean I don't like how this is being
politicized. Um you know it was meant to
it was a political act and uh treating
it as a political act just validates
what the killer did.
>> Yeah. I agree. I agree. I'll tell you
another thing too, Ted, about this this
poor Charlie Kirk thing. Um,
almost all of my friends, like real
friends, not just Facebook friends,
people I I've never really met,
whether they're from the left or the
right or someplace in between, everybody
is absolutely appalled by this. And
everybody is afraid of the direction
that the country is taking. You and I
were talking about it yesterday um after
the show. I talked about it with my
brother and sister last night. My son
was so upset, he called me at 10:30 to
say he's just so upset about this
Charlie Kirk thing. and and he's, you
know, at least as left as I am. But this
I hope this serves as a wakeup call for
the country. And I keep coming back to
this.
>> It's not because we don't have aid the
leadership.
>> We don't like literally the person who's
supposed to tell us stop acting like
[__] children and grow up and and and
and understand the difference between
words and violence. Yeah. and and
understand that free speech you don't
there's no there's no obligation for
anyone to speak in such a way that you
won't take offense um and like and and
you know and stop you know and and like
if an American dies from murder that
that's an American who died not a
right-winger or a left-winger um it's
like
>> it's an American
>> it's a young a young father which
bothers me very very much
>> me too it's right in front of him by the
way and not to mention traumatizing
hundreds of of college students out and
trying to enjoy a nice day. Disgusting.
And so the point is, but Donald Trump is
politicizing this. And um you know, I
mean, I'm not going to go so far as to
say like he's
>> responsible for this because I don't
think it works that way. But I do think
that um he he's not providing the
leadership that we need to to be able to
have this be like a snap out of our
[__] moment.
>> Ted, let me interrupt you for a minute
for two things. Number one, Robbie's
telling us we have an ad. But I want to
thank
>> Chris MZTZ TC too. Thank you for the
donation. Got a He's got a great
question here, Ted. Uh, regarding the
New York Times article about the Seal
Team 6 mission in North Korea. How does
the story like that leak out? Wouldn't
it be a national security risk to expose
that? And if in charge, would I approve?
Oh, that what a great three questions.
So, number one, somebody who opposed it.
and was overruled. Leaked that story
>> 100%.
>> And I can tell you that from my own
experience at the CIA, 99 times out of
100, the leak came from the Pentagon.
>> They leak like saves over there and
they're so gigantic and they don't
polygraph anybody that it's just
impossible to know where the leaks came
from. Number one, how does a story like
that leak out? Okay, wouldn't it be a
national security risk to expose it? You
bet it is. Of course, his methods, it
exposes methodology.
>> Kim Jong Kim Jong-un knows something now
that he didn't know before.
>> That's right.
>> You know, he's gonna be more.
>> Yep.
>> Okay, let me read Let me read this ad.
Looking for a comfortable but unique
option for your gaming setup. Check out
technasportusa.com.
With a wide array of ergonomic chairs in
an array of colors, you will definitely
bring your setup to the next level.
Always comfy, never boring. Technosport.
Use code rumble for 10% off your entire
order. That sounds good. I want one
myself.
>> I like that.
>> I like I'm I'm a [__] for a comfortable
chair.
>> You know, I got to say, too, when we got
our first ad on YouTube, it was REI. And
I really like REI. I was so proud that
it was them and not like, you know,
erectile dysfunction or something
because you knew that was coming
>> or not coming. That's what I'm um Oh my
god. So, so
yeah, I mean, okay. So then, and by the
way, if in charge, would you have
approved of this operation?
>> Absolutely not. Because if you compare
the the upside to the to the risk of
blowback, the risk of blowback in my
view is too great. I wouldn't have
approved it.
>> All right, let me ask you a bigger
question. Are Seal Team Six a bunch of
tards? I mean, they mess up a lot,
right?
>> A lot. So,
>> and not only do they mess up a lot, a
lot of them get killed in the course of
the operation.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. No,
>> I mean, are they too I mean, I know you
do need people who are badass and brave
and willing to do whatever, but
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But but you also want you want you want
your people to come home.
>> You don't want your to be exposed.
>> Yep. That is right. Uh Robbie's telling
us we have breaking news. What kind of
breaking news is that, Robbie?
>> Let's hear it. I bet I bet the suspect's
been caught.
Robbie.
>> Oh, let me put Robbie on.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Hey, Robbie. What's going on?
>> Hi.
>> Uh, so just popped up that uh Cash
Patel, he's in a little bit of hot water
for calling Uncle Twice about saying
that they had the guy. Turned out they
didn't. And so now he is personally in
Utah overseeing the investigation. So
the the clown has left the circus and is
now running the peanut gallery. So,
we're in good hands.
>> Oh my god. Hi, Robbie. Well, that's not
exactly startling, but it is funny.
>> Oh, it's hilarious.
>> You know, and JD Vance and his wife are
there, too.
>> And you know, I was supposed to I was
supposed to fly down to uh Fort
Lauderdale on Monday to do James
O'Keefe's show, and I just got a text
from him cancelling it because Charlie
Kirk's going to be buried on Monday, and
he's going to go to the funeral. Yeah,
apparently um uh Vice President Vance
and the second lady are going to escort
uh Charlie's remains uh on Air Force 2,
uh to Arizona. Um I guess from Utah. I
guess that's where um Charlie Kirk is
from or he's going to be laid to rest.
Um you know,
Robbie, you called, by the way, that
what kind of long gun you thought would
probably
>> You really did. You said specifically it
was a 30 odd six and it was a 30 odd
six.
>> Why did you think that and that's what
was recovered in the in the woods near
the university?
>> Well, a couple of reasons. One, it's if
you're going to make that kind of a
shot, you want to use a boltaction
rifle. 30 six is a proven round. It's
over 100 years old and you can either
run them hot or you can run them cold
depending on, you know, on what is
you're looking for. And they have a very
they have a very specific report. And so
if you shoot a lot like I do, u you get
to know what what it sounds like. And
the people saying that like kind of like
that turkey you were talking to earlier,
John, about you got to be a a
professional sniper to do something like
this.
>> No, you don't.
>> No. If if you're I have an old Argentine
mouser that was made in Germany back in
the 1890s.
>> Is that a It's a single shot. Yeah.
>> Yeah. B It's a bolt action. So what you
do it has a five round magazine and just
what's what's neat about them
>> is that the barrels are milled. They're
not stamps have really deep grooves
>> and whenever you're you know you can
make a two to 400 yard shot with with
iron sights behind the ear of a deer
with no problem at all.
>> Wow.
>> And and what it is is it's a heavy
bullet. So what you're talking about is
right. What you do is that you aim
higher what is that you're going for
because you got this because you got
drift.
>> Yeah.
>> Well that's what happened. I think most
likely he was aiming for his face. The
bullet drifted and it got him in the
neck and either way it's a kill shot.
The job is done. If you're hunting deer,
that's what you want. Hunting a person.
I don't know. Guess depends on how much
of a mesh you want to make.
>> All right, Robbie, thanks for that. I'm
We'll uh And that was that really was I
was kind of amazed that you were able to
to call it that way.
>> You called it.
>> Hey, I Hey, I grew up in the South
shooting. I mean, this is not hard.
>> Yes, you did. And by the way, I strongly
recommend anybody who hasn't heard it
yet to go into Rumble Studio uh Rumble
Premium and watch the uh Robbie
interview. And by the way, John, we're
uh doing the we're doing five tomorrow.
All right, cool. Looking forward to
that.
>> It's going to be all about prison.
>> Oh, question for Robbie. I'm going to
put Robbie back up here. $5 donation
from USCX A-Rod 21. As a person of the
right, are you comfortable with people
like uh Bonino and Patel running
agencies like this?
>> Good question. It seems like these guys
are always swimming.
>> If I had it my way, the FBI would have
been abolished the very first day of
Trump's presidency because he
Trump promised to to drain the swamp.
Well, the way that you drain the swamp
is by gutting it. You don't go in but
say, "I'm going to give you a brand
spanking new headquarters." Now, the
Trump is Trump is just a total blowhard.
If I had it my way, it would be gone.
The CIA would be destroyed. The FBI
would no longer exist. Another question
for you, Robbie. Sorry to interrupt, but
it's what I do. Uh, Tusk PC wants to
know, "I thought you were blind in one
eye. How good of a shot are you?"
>> Uh, used to be really good. Uh, now not
so much. I'm having to having to teach
myself how to shoot left-handed using a
22. So, it's a pain.
>> Oh, [__] It's like learning how to
drive uh using the stick on the left.
Uh, which
>> Oh, it sucks in England. Yeah. But not
but I mean growing up I mean I used to
hunt squirrels and rabbits all the time
using a single shot 22.
>> If you're doing that you know shooting a
deer with a 30 six it's not a problem.
>> No I mean the thing is also God I
remember living living in Long Island
you could just drive your car up to a
deer and it'd be 10 feet away from you
and you could just pop it point blank
range. I mean I have to beep I beep at
them behind my house to get out of the
way. I gotta go.
>> Yeah. They're they're kind of like not
they're not really that that
>> I saw a big buck the other day. I'm like
beeping at the buck, flashing my my
brights at him like get off the road for
God's sake.
>> Uh here we have elk walking down the
road.
>> I mean those are big boys.
>> Oh yeah.
>> All right, Robbie. Thanks for that.
We'll let you know if you have if we
have more questions. Um I I really do
love this question uh from JR99
over on the YouTube feed. Why do why
don't we have Why doesn't security for
outdoor events use drones for
surveillance?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> That's a [__] good question.
>> It is. It's cheap.
>> It's easy.
>> There's no reason not to.
>> No. I mean, the thing is I I wonder how
much security there really was here.
Like, I mean, obviously there was a
threat, but I mean, they didn't treat
him like he was the president of the
United States. And no, I don't really
blame them. I mean, you know, he's just
if they he's an influencer. He's
>> But still, Ted,
>> a million of those.
>> Still Ted, the the the building where
they're telling us the the shooter was
on the roof, that building closed down
for renovation in April and was supposed
to be locked up tight. And did it not
occur to anybody in in the campus police
department to just, you know, sweep the
the building, walk up to the roof, just
make sure nobody's up there?
>> I mean, by the way, I mean, where did we
where did we hear about something very
similar in the very recent past? a
gunman kicking around on the roof,
right? I mean, it's like just this is
what happened to to Trump in Butler,
Pennsylvania. Um it's you would think by
now it would be kind of a standard
operating procedure.
>> Um I got to ask you also um what do you
make of the fact that uh the cartridges
uh bearing quote unquote transgender and
anti-fascist inscriptions.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh were written. I mean I has that been
confirmed? It it's been confirmed
according by to the authorities. So I'm
wondering if Luigi Manion was an
inspiration. I've never heard of anyone
doing that before.
>> Never. Now that would take work. You
know, you can't just like go to the gun
shop and say, "Let give me some of those
trans bullets, right? That's not how it
works.
There's work involved."
>> I I I thought I was a 45, but now I
identify as a 38.
>> Oh my god. I'm a 38 in the trapped in
the body of a of a 9 millimeter. Like,
no, it's hilarious.
>> I I don't know. I don't know what to
make of it. It's one of those
>> I've got to think it's a So, this is I I
I really think we're going to find out
this was a Luigi thing and that the
person was inspired by Luigi. I think
we're going to find that out. Similar
age.
>> This is bad.
>> Someone in their 20s.
>> Yeah. You know, if they catch
>> him telling us if if they c they'll
catch it
in which you we have a photo of someone
like that. Fuzzy, but a photo and
they're not caught.
>> Oh, no. No. They've further enhanced it
about an hour ago. It this looks to be
as clear as, you know, some kid's high
school graduation picture. And And
besides that,
>> he left a a hand print. Yeah. Palm
print.
>> Yeah. an a print from his arm and his
face was sweaty where he had the gun up
against his face. So, he left DNA all
over the dog on thing. He threw it in
the He threw the gun in the woods. It
hasn't rained or anything. The cops
found the gun. This This kid is an idiot
and he's going to get caught. He's going
to get caught.
>> Luigi was an idiot. He left a bag of
evidence in Central Park.
>> Yeah. Nobody Yeah. Nobody ever goes
there,
>> right? and then took off his mask so he
could flirt with the girl at the uh at
the youth hostel.
>> Absurd
>> idiot.
>> Yeah, total idiot. Um yeah.
>> All right, so let's see what else here.
Um
uh okay,
so
anyone Yeah. Hamish McKinnus is saying
anyone who knew the person of interest
would recognize them from that photo.
>> Absolutely.
>> I don't think there's any world in which
they get away with it. No way.
>> Yeah.
>> No way. I agree.
>> It's just a matter It's only a matter of
time. I just hope that when the person's
caught that he's caught alive. First of
all, we don't need more death. And
secondly, I I want to know what the
motivation is. Uh the Butler,
Pennsylvania thing, we're never going to
really know what happened because he's
dead.
>> Exactly.
Yeah. Exactly. And then they create they
they gave the body back to the families
so they could cremate him before anybody
ever had a chance to uh to even examine
him.
>> Big boss Bob Ross is correct. He said
Luigi took her off the mask at the
hostel because it was required for
check-in. Okay, but Bob
>> Yeah, but Bob, he could have said [__]
you and left. I mean, it's it's
Manhattan. Okay, there are hundreds of
hotels. Okay. I mean, he could have gone
somewhere else, right? Um, let's see. We
have a a $5 donation from uh Air Linked
Up. Thank you very much. What's going on
with all this UFO stuff? It seems like
it's being used as a distraction. Every
time there's bad economic data coming
out, um, Alzando seems like a grifter.
Would like to hear your thoughts. The
economic data is really [__] bad and
it's a topic that we're not talking
about. I mean, you know, John, uh, you
and I are old enough to know that like,
um, job creation of 22,000
is catastrophic. I mean, usually that
means you're in the middle of a of a
hardcore recession. Um, and it would
have been it could have been worse um,
if not for all the deportations, right?
I mean, so
>> it does look like uh, you know, our our
friend uh, Mr. Laura is correct and that
we are headed towards stagflation
which is not good. Inflation with a
stagnant economy is is a worst is really
not the worst but it's a very bad
scenario.
>> I mean
>> it it cost Jimmy Carter his presidency
and it took us what 10 years to dig out
of eight years to dig out of.
>> It sure did.
>> So yeah it's this is this is
>> I would argue that we didn't get a real
recovery until the 90s. I think you are
right because really the the Reagan
recovery was a false one. Yeah. And it
was a false one because you can't cut
taxes and increase spending at the same
time and then just hope like magic that
the economy grows because all the rich
people are spending the the tax money
that they didn't have to pay.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean at least they're
collecting money from tariffs. But uh as
Benjamin Drew Ho says, I like how they
celebrate the amount of money coming in
from tariffs like it isn't a tax on all
US consumers. companies. Yeah, that's us
paying that. Um, it would almost be more
honest if they just slammed it. Um, you
know, Robbie says, "We've been in a
depression here in Montana for years."
Fair enough.
>> That's kind of stagflation what they
have there. Actually, high prices,
>> you know, just no jobs. Just as we were
coming on the air, I got my my, you
know, five days a week, I guess it's six
days a week, uh, hyper local news
update, and it said that, um, housing
prices in Arlington, Virginia, as well
as DC and Alexandria, Virginia, are down
4.1% year-over-year. This is the first
drop in housing prices in close-in
suburban Washington since 1991.
Can you imagine?
>> This is the urban problem that again
nobody's talking about. I mean, COVID
accelerated it, right? Yeah.
>> But with work at home, you don't need to
live in a city, right? I mean, why I
mean, I loved living I when I I went to
college as a freshman here in New York
in 1981. I mean, think about like my
first week in school. The first week in
school, I was photographed uh in Time
magazine throwing a bottle at Mayor
Cotch. I went to see Blondie at uh at at
the Peppermint Lounge for three bucks
with sawdust on the floor. Um I went to
Studio 54. Wow.
>> All in the same week, right? I mean, I
raged. I lost my virginity. It was
awesome. Like now, if I'm 20, if I'm 18
years old, why the what the [__] is it
do? What am I going to do? Sephora? Um,
there's there's no nightclubs, there's
nothing to do, you don't have a there's
your job will be from your computer,
which you can do anywhere. Um, you know,
it's it's boring and hard and expensive.
>> That's not a that and you don't need you
don't need to be in a city to date
anymore. You know, you have the apps for
that. So,
>> that's right.
>> So, I don't know. I feel like cities are
in trouble and um you know, they're
going to have to become cheaper in order
to adjust.
>> Thanks for the donation, Angela. Much
appreciated.
Yeah, I think you're I think you're
exactly right. My first my first week um
at college freshman year, Abby Hoffman
came to campus and gave a speech.
>> How awesome is that?
>> Isn't that great?
>> Yeah.
>> I still remember, still think about it
every once in a while. He committed
suicide not too long after that. But but
he was great. Really great. He had gone
to one of the uh fraternities earlier in
the day and he bought somebody's old TV
and then he plugged it in. Reagan was
giving a nationally televised talk for
whatever reason. This would have been in
August of 1982.
And so while while Reagan was talking,
the TV was just sitting on a on a
folding chair up on the stage. While
Reagan was talking, Abby Hoffman walked
off stage, walked back on with a
sledgehammer, and smashed the TV to a
million pieces.
>> [__] people were screaming, cheering.
>> It's great.
>> That's so punk rock. That's so I love
that. Speaking of punk rock, I saw the
Clash that year, too. Um,
>> and the Ramones and the Dead Kennedies.
Oh my gosh.
>> It was awesome. You know, none of that
stuff's true anymore. And it's not like,
oh, I know it's all different bands, but
the music scene, there is no music scene
the way there used to be. Um,
>> no.
>> Anyway, let's talk a little bit about uh
we can just check in. Do we care about
uh Jer Balssonaro? I mean, so
>> yeah, convicted,
>> but I think the reason we should care,
I'm sorry to interrupt you, Ted. I think
the reason we should care is that Donald
Trump has threatened already to put
sanctions on all of the Brazilian
Supreme Court justices were they to find
him guilty. So now they found him
guilty. And not only is Trump now
discussing sanctions on the judges, he's
talking about sanctions against Lula,
which is a really dumb idea because God
knows Donald Trump has a lot more
investment in Brazil than Lula has
probably zero dollars investment in the
United States. And what is there to stop
Lula from from sanctioning Donald Trump
and freezing his Brazilian assets,
>> which he has?
>> There you go.
Good. Uh well, we'll see what happens
there. Um all right, let's get to uh
something that is that does really has
has me furious. Um so you remember of
course obviously the Venezuelan vote
that the administration uh bragged about
on social media. They they said it was
Trenda Ara quote unquote terrorists
because they have designated Trend Ara
terrorist organization. It was a boat
headed between uh from Venezuela
apparently to Trinidad. Um they blew it
up with a drone. We now know that it was
with a drone. We thought it was for
drone. Just it looked like drone
footage. 11 people dead according to the
Defense Department. So anyway, it turns
out that finally they've gotten around
to briefing the the the the the uh gang
of four people, right? So uh Senate
Armed Services uh Committee Chairman
Jack Reid um came out of the briefing
pissed off. So he said that there was no
evidence presented in the briefing
whatsoever that said that the targets
were armed, posed any threat, were
members of Trende Aaragua, were carrying
drugs, were headed to the United States,
were even from Venezuela.
No evidence of anything. These were 11
random people that they killed for no
reason whatsoever
and that's it. And so, um, you know, I'm
sure Jack Reed's not lying. If he was
lying, uh, the administration would have
been quick to point it out. Um,
this is really, I mean, I hate to say
it, you and I, we knew this was probably
going to be true or might be true, but
it's like I hate to be disappointed like
this. I mean, I hate to be proven right
in something like this. I wanted them to
I mean, it wouldn't have been legal even
if these guys were trending Aaragua,
even if they were drug dealers. wouldn't
have been legal. They should have
interdicted them.
>> But agree
>> and it's not even our business. They
weren't even coming to the United
States. I mean,
>> no, they weren't.
>> Trinidad and authorities didn't ask for
help.
>> So, I mean, this is But this is no one's
going to give a [__] because they're
brown people, right?
>> Yeah, I think that's exactly right, Ted.
Nobody's going to give a [__] And most
Americans just take the White House's
word for it. No matter or the Pentagon's
word, no matter who happens to be in
charge, if if it fits into the national
narrative that these whoever these guys
were on this boat were terrorists, were
trend rau tren de aragua or were
carrying cocaine or whatever. They're
just going to jump up at them and say,
"Great." Now, I think that the chances
are pretty good that these were just
fishermen who saw, you know, whatever it
was, a ship in the distance or drones in
the distance and said, "Oh crap, let's
get back to port." And turned around and
started to rush back and then got
rocketed.
Terrible.
>> Yeah. I mean, that's the thing, too,
right? the um you know the US Supreme
Court ruled a long time ago that if you
come up to a police checkpoint and then
you run away from the cops because
you're afraid of the cops. Yeah, that
does not provide the police with
probable cause. But that's exactly the
rationale that the administration used
to say that uh they were right to blow
up this boat. They said that the boat
spotted the drone and then turned seemed
to turn away from it. I don't know about
you, if I saw an armed drone approach
me, I'd turn away from it, too. Doesn't
mean I'm trying or that I'm Venezuelan
or that I'm carrying drugs or anything
else.
>> No, that's exactly right.
We've had a question about UAPs and uh
and Alzando, I forget his first name,
but he's like Mr. UAP these days. Um,
you think he's a grifter?
I've I've tried to I've tried to walk a
fine line on this issue. Um but I saw
what I saw when I was 16 17 years old.
I've told that story and um I I don't I
can't deny anybody else the account of
their own personal experience. But I
also don't understand why the Pentagon
doesn't just release this information or
why the White House doesn't just
declassify the information, why it has
to leak out, and why we have to have
people being called to testify on
Capitol Hill as whistleblowers, risking
their own imprisonment,
you know, were they to be charged under
the Espionage Act, just to say, "Yeah,
I'm a I'm an F-18 pilot and I saw this
thing moving at a fant fantastic speed
and it paralleled me and then it took
off at, you know, the speed of light
practically.
And then the Pentagon denies that any
such thing has taken place. For a long
time, and you'll remember this, um there
was worry that if if the government were
to admit that there were UAPs or UFOs,
um that people would panic. Well, the
word leaked out and nobody gave a [__]
There was no panic. Everybody,
>> they had more faith than us back then.
They thought we that we might have a we
might have a pulse.
>> See, that's right.
>> That we might react to something.
>> That's right.
>> Apparently nothing. You know, it would
be like it would be like not the day
that the Earth stood still. It would be
like the day that the Earth kept looking
at its phone.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. You know,
yesterday was the anniversary of of the
disappearance of this Australian pilot.
I'm sure you've heard of this uh this
case. There's this Australian pilot in
his early 20s. I think he was 23 years
old. He was flying. It was It was
September 10th, 1978. I saw several
different references to this yesterday.
He's flying and he said that there was a
a silver cylinder above his plane flying
at exactly the same rate of speed. And
then he's radioing back saying, "There's
this thing. It's right on top of me and
it's it's flying the same rate of speed.
I don't know what it is." He's
describing it. It's silver. It's shiny.
Um, and then he came back and he said,
"It's not it's not an aircraft," he
said. And then there was this loud sound
of like electronic interference.
Nobody ever saw him or heard from him
again. They never found him. They never
found the plane. They never found
anything.
So why, you know, why keep that secret?
Why not just say, "Hey, look, there's
something up there. We don't know what
the heck it is,
>> right?" I mean, there you have it.
>> I mean, that's the thing, right?
Originally, right, unidentified does not
mean alien. That's
>> exactly unidentified.
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
>> yeah.
>> Yeah. So, let's see. Um,
>> you know, let me let me say one more
thing about Luis Alzando. Um, when I had
my show on RT, people used to tell me
all the all the time, "You have to have
Luis Alzando on. He's an expert. He's an
expert. He's an expert." So, I I did
some research and what I found was
him saying repeatedly that he's an
expert.
I don't know what the heck he's an
expert on, but he sure likes to get out
there and be the UFO guy. And it it just
wasn't it it wasn't a fit for me. So I
have this rule John which is that if
someone voluntarily says some that
describes themsself as having a positive
attribute
they not only don't have that attribute
they are the opposite. So if someone
just sort of says you know like if you
like if I ask you John are you a good
tipper and you say yeah that's not what
I'm talking about. I'm like if you just
say Ted by the way you know I I tip
really great. I'm a [__] great
tipper. waiters love me, then I know
you're a tight wad for sure and that
everyone hates you and that and there's
spit in all of your food everywhere in
the DC metro area. Um, and that's what
someone if someone says, "Oh, you know,
by the way, I'm an expert on blah blah
blah." No one who's actually an expert
ever says that you know it's like they
they just are and people talk to them
about that topic and you know no one no
one you know no one has to ask you about
the you know like you're never saying
well by the way I John Kuraku an expert
in this and that you just are and you
know that's how it is like you know like
on a date if a if someone says oh you
know I'm really good in bed oh man I
mean I I lay I lay tight like you you
will be [__] screaming You you you
will lose track of who you are. You'll
lose see you'll you'll space time will
change. That's a lie. You know you know
you're like dead bed. All right, let me
read this ad here.
>> Yeah.
>> Ready to level up your game? Aim
controllers is where custom beats un
meets unbeatable value. And right now
it's the best deal of the year. We start
with official Sony and Xbox controllers.
Fully compatible with console and PC. No
functionality lost. Then you go wild
with custom features. Smart bumpers,
paddles, grips, stick height, custom
buttons, even design your own PS5 snap
panels. And here's the part no one else
is doing. Lifetime warranty on all
modified parts. That's right, lifetime.
What other company does that exactly?
Normally, a fully loaded setup could run
you $400, but during our one price
promo, it's just $29
or $182, no matter how many features you
add. Use code rumble at checkout and
lock it in. This is your sign. Go to
aimcontrollers.com
and build the last controller you'll
ever need. That sounds appealing. And I
don't even game.
>> I I wanna I want to say one other thing,
too. I was sitting next to this guy at
this 911 truther lunch today and um he
was telling me how interested he is in
this in this issue and he he's talked to
everybody who's out there to talk to and
he starts naming people and he mentions
Susan Lindau.
And so I I said to him, "Be careful of
Susan Lindau."
And he asked me why. And I said,
"Honestly, I believe she's a fraud." And
he said, "What do you mean if she's a
fraud? She was the secret back channel
to Saddam Hussein." And I said, "Exactly
my point." No, she wasn't. And I said,
"I actually confronted her. There was
this big whistleblower event. It's the
only one that she somehow got into. It
was on the roof of the Hey Adams Hotel
here in Washington across the street
from the White House. And um I was
shocked to see her there and she came up
to me and introduced herself and I was
kind of cold and I said, "Oh yes, I I
know who you are and um and she
confronted me and she asked me why I
wasn't
uh friendlier, more supportive." Besides
the fact that when she was prosecuted,
they actually ended up dropping the
charges because she was uh mentally
unable, like she was too insane to be
tried, so they just dropped the charges.
>> Um, but I said to her, "Look, I'll tell
you the truth.
You tell everybody that you were the
secret back channel to Saddam Hussein,
and I know you're lying. And the reason
I know you're lying is because I briefed
the secret back channel to Saddam
Hussein and it wasn't you.
>> Oh man.
>> And I I said to him, he says, "Oh, come
on. Come on. I find that hard to
believe." I said, "You know, I've never
said the name, but I'm going to say the
name because the Secret Back channel is
dead. He's dead now. So, I'm going to
say the name." I said when I was in
Bahrain, we got a cable from the state
department saying David Rockefeller is
coming to the to Bahrain to accept an
award from the Bahrain US Banking
Society and give him the red carpet
treatment and give him what's called a
country team briefing. So a country team
briefing is the ambassador, the deputy
chief of mission, the head of the
economic section, the head of the
political section, the head of public
affairs, the head of everything. if
there's a station chief there, he gets
the full classified briefing.
So, he flew in on a Thursday. The
weekend in Bahrain is Thursday and
Friday. He flew in and I was his control
officer. So, I picked him up in the in
the embassy's, you know, giant Cadillac
and there was a red carpet and we went
straight to the embassy, did the full
classified country team briefing and
then the Amir had a big dinner for him.
The whole cabinet was invited. The
entire diplomatic corps was invited. Big
big dinner at the palace. There was a
there was a receding line. So we shake
hands with the Amir and the prime
minister and the crown prince and Mr.
Rockefeller.
So a couple of days later, well a a day
later, he had his ceremony at the
Bahrain US Banking Society. They give
him his little trophy and then he
leaves.
So, Saturday, which was the first day of
the work week, I go into the
ambassador's office for the morning
meeting, and he said, "So, Mr.
Rockefeller got off okay." And I said,
"Yeah, he got off okay. It was really
cool meeting him." But I said, "But why
would a guy who's almost a hundred years
old fly halfway around the world to
collect a little trophy from some
banking organization nobody's ever heard
of?" And the ambassador goes, "John,
John, John, you're supposed to be the
smart one." And I said, I said, "What?
What am I missing here?"
And the station chief starts to laugh.
And the ambassador says, "John, he's the
secret back channel to Saddam Hussein.
This was his cover stop."
And I was like, "Oh my god, I'm such an
idiot." Which is why we gave him the
classified briefing. And he said,
"Exactly." So I said to Susan Lindau,
"It wasn't you, Susan Lindau.
You were not the secret back channel to
Saddam Hussein."
>> Unless um she used to be a dude and she
used to be dead, so she's trans alive
and trans female.
>> Yeah. And another thing, too, this was
the press secretary. She was the press
secretary to a firstterm congressman
from New Jersey. And she says that the
CIA secretly chose her to fly out to
Saddam Hussein and tell him, "Listen,
you better start uh towing the line,
Saddam Hussein." And I'm like, "Yeah,
that never happened."
>> You know, John, being it really strikes
me like this, you know, like being in
the CIA because people aren't allowed to
talk about their experiences, it just
opens up this this space for all these
liars to basically say that they did
that and the other. Reminds me a little
bit of the journalists that I knew in
Afghanistan.
>> Or who would make things up and they'd
be like, "No one's ever going to check
out my story in [__] you know,
Mazzari Sharif. I can say whatever." And
it's like, and for the most part, they
were right. I mean, no one ever, you
know, never no one ever knew anything. I
had a
>> I knew a guy who uh worked for um Travel
and Leisure. Sorry, K, I'm lying. Kai
Nas Traveler and he wrote this piece.
This flowery piece magazine.
>> Yeah. He wrote this flowery piece. I c I
couldn't get published in there. Flowery
piece about uh taking the train from
Ashkabbat Turk Menistan to Mashad Iran
and talked about how beautiful it was,
the the lace curtains on the windows,
how good the tea was. And I'm like, man,
I would love to take that [__] train.
>> But that train has never been
constructed.
It's been and so the reason that he
thought it lonely planet guide said it's
expected to be construct to be completed
in two years. Well, the Lonely Planet
Guide was four years old. So the [__]
picked up a copy and assumed it must be
done by now.
>> I called up, you know, and
>> not cool at all.
>> And this [__] happens all the time.
>> Without a doubt. Hey, uh we should we
should plug the good people at Rumble.
>> Yes,
>> they've been very good to us.
>> Yes. Thank you very much, Rumble. um for
uh well anyway, please come over to
Rumble and watch us over there. That's
the main thing. Uh because we make more
money there and they've been very
supportive and we're in the Rumble
creative program. Uh and so uh and we
have Rumble premium content over there.
For $5 a month, you can watch the us and
the Rumble premium content and you get
like a special little doodad when you
comment. And for 10 bucks a month, you
can see you can have those privileges
for all content over on Rumble. So,
please do that. Um, also, uh, USCX
A-Rod 21 has, I would say, been
patiently waiting, but has been waiting.
I don't know if they're patient or not.
Um, John, come on. There's aliens,
right? Parts of the government have to
know.
>> There have to be
that. There have to be. I mean, maybe
they're just little bacteria. Who knows?
But uh yeah, I was talking to a guy the
other day, a guy who like he presents as
very serious
and he was telling me that um that uh
he's doing a book about Area 58. And I
said, "Aar 51?" He said, "No, Area 58.
It's even
>> 51 plus seven
>> plus seven more." And it's that much
more secret. and that there's an
underground bunker at Area 58
>> and that is where the alien ships come
in to land and we call it the embassy
because that's where that's where we
liaz with the uh the aliens. I'm like,
"Okay." And but you know what? I mean,
I've learned so much about government
after having left government that that
who knows. And Algerian Corsair, forgive
me. Okay. You wanted to hear about um
about uh this 9/11
truth thing
>> and then we have to get to Iran Contra
before
>> we do. We have to get to Iran Contra.
So, I've got a friend who's a PR guy and
he ran into some really bad he ran into
a really bad period in life. His wife
left him. He lost his job. People that
used to work for him sued him. He was
arrested. It was just bad. But listen,
I'm I'm one of the most loyal people out
there. And so, he's still my friend, and
I wanted to express, you know, support.
So, he's finally getting back on his
feet again. He's still doing PR, but he
used to do PR for for Julian Assange and
Wikileaks and all these left-wing groups
and Ed Snowden. And now he does PR for
the far right because
they pay him and the far left walked
away. The far left, the left walked away
from him. And so he asked me a few weeks
ago, hey, uh, on the anniversary of 911,
would you give a speech about, you know,
what 911 meant to you or whatever? I
said, yeah, sure. He said, I'll give you
$500. I said, okay, great.
That was it. That was the extent of it.
And then somebody saw a poster for 911
911 engineers and architects
fortruth.org
or whatever. And it's featuring, you
know, John Kiryaku and all these people
who I've always considered to be like
deeply insane.
And I was like, "Dog gone it, Trevor.
You put me with a 9/11 truth
organization." And he's like, "Yeah,
well, didn't you do your due diligence?"
And I said, 'N no, I trusted you. We're
friends. You asked me to do it. I said,
' Okay.
So, my my sister called me. She's like,
"What are you doing?" I said, "I know. I
know. I" And she says, "You have to
withdraw." And I said, "I can't. I I
made a commitment. I have to stand by my
commitments." And I I decided I've
thought about this a lot the last couple
of weeks, but I decided that I'm going
to give my speech tonight. And of all
people, Dennis Cusinich is introducing
me. I'm gonna give my speech tonight and
I'm gonna say, "Look,
you and I will never ever agree on
whether or not building 7 was controlled
demolition. I'll never believe that it
was. I will never believe that such a
thing as thermite paint exists and is
suddenly somehow spontaneously
explosive."
>> That does not exist.
>> It doesn't exist. There is no such a
thing. applied physics major, Columbia
School of Engineering and Applied
Science. No nuclear engineering
originally,
>> but
I can take a [__] on the Saudis for
hours without even taking a breath and
on the Israelis both relative to the
9/11 attacks. And so for sure, that's
what I'm going to do.
>> And and the Pakistanis probably have
[__] upon to be done.
>> That's right. So there it is.
>> Um Okay. So, let's talk about the uh
this is a funny story. So, um the Iran
Contra scandal of the late 1980s is back
in the news because Ali North has
finally married his former secretary
Fawn Hall, who was famously smuggling
classified documents out in her bazir.
>> Yeah, I was I was if you saw her bra,
what was what she was packing back then,
you were jealous of those classified
documents.
>> Yes, you were. She was beautiful.
Stunning.
>> So, they just got married four decades
after all of this. It was always assumed
that they were stooping.
>> Yeah.
>> But they weren't.
>> Apparently, they weren't.
>> They were both loyal to their spouses at
the time. Yeah.
>> Um Colonel North, 81 years old now, and
uh Ms. Hall, 65,
>> um still young. Um were married on
August 27th at a civil ceremony there in
Arlington County.
>> Yeah.
>> Um the So, Ms. North and uh Mr. North's
wife of 56 years and the mother of their
four children died in November at the
age of 80. Ms. Hall had previously been
married I love this part.
>> I was shocked by this
>> to to Danny Sugarman who managed the
doors.
>> He managed the doors of all things
>> and he died in 2005. 50 years old. Lung
cancer.
>> Yeah.
>> How did he manage the doors?
Come on. Come on. Come on now. Touch me
babe. You know I go through I I for me I
go through I I have all of their records
and their CDs. I love the Doors, but I
go through phases like where I suddenly
am like, wait, they're kind of hacks and
I shouldn't listen to them anymore. And
then I then I'm like, oh, I miss them so
much. They're great. And then I have to
play them incessantly. Does that make
any sense? I mean, you know, it I never
liked the fact that Jim Morrison was
obsessed with Frank Sinatra and was
trying to sound like Frank Sinatra
>> and Sinatra hated him.
>> Yeah. Well, Frank Sinatra was a very
serious person. Yeah.
>> And Jim and Jim Morrison was a [__]
mess.
>> Yeah.
>> So, he was incredibly unreliable. I
mean, you feel sorry for the rest of the
band.
>> Uh, speaking of a Doors connection, I'm
gonna see X soon. And, uh, what's his
name from the Doors? Produced the first
um X album, Los Angeles.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, Ray Manzer.
>> Rayman Zerk.
>> Yeah. He's a producer. Big- time
producer at the time. He's he's a
musical genius who's
>> Yeah.
>> who's very humble and quiet and and does
not really promote his genius.
>> Reed is saying that uh marshals have
been deployed to Utah. I would need more
details about that.
>> Oh,
>> let's see what Let's see what the
interwebs have to say about that. What
for though, you know?
>> Wow. Okay. I mean, is this to go out to
I'm not I'm not seeing anything. All
right. Well, whatever. Okay.
>> Awesome. Well, lots of news today.
>> So, yeah, for sure. So, anyway, I want
to just say that like uh we talked about
this earlier before we went on the air,
but uh John, you and I both agree that
uh we wish we wish uh Ali North and uh
Fawn Hall nothing but the best.
>> True love.
I do think
>> I don't agree at all with what Ali North
did or what Fon Hall did.
>> Right.
>> Right. Nor do I. Nor nor do I. But I
wish them happiness. I think it's nice.
>> Totally. Totally. Yeah. So,
uh, hey, thief. Uh, back off. I love
that Ted name dropped the dead Kennedys.
Y'all showing boomers can be co cool.
Gen X, not Boomer. All right.
Just saying.
>> All right.
>> We're boomers.
>> Demographically, we're boomers.
>> 46 to 64.
>> Okay. But listen, the thing is 1961 to
1964, those are cusp kids. We get to
choose our generation.
>> That's right.
>> Because and and I'm take and the high I
get it from the highest authority.
Douglas Copeland, who wrote Generation
X, def in 1990, defined Generation X at
that time as anyone then in their 20s,
which meant anyone born in the 60s,
>> right? That's just arithmetic.
>> I'll take that.
>> I've obviously thought about this. So
anyway, I used I used to be obsessed
with generational politics, but just
because I like the Doras doesn't mean
that I'm not far more partial to
Flipper.
>> Yeah. Yeah. True. True.
>> All right. So, all right everybody,
thanks so much for joining us. We really
appreciate you. Uh, really truly, we
really appreciate you. Um, and so this
is Drogram with Ted Roll and John
Kuryaki. We are here Monday through
Friday, 5:00 PM Eastern time. We'll be
back Friday, tomorrow at 5:00 PM Eastern
to bring you up to date and deprogram
you from everything. Hope that you're
you consider yourself sufficiently
deprogrammed, John. I know I do. And
like, follow, and share the show.
Thanks. uh producer Robbie for uh your
assistance and gun expertise which we
will call upon in the future.
>> Yes indeed.
>> Ciao.